# Mykhailo

Full Stack Developer Zaporizhzhya, Ukraine

Mykhailo is a dedicated Full-Stack developer with 8+ years of experience. He is dedicated and responsible. Often thinks out of the box and suggests alternative ways to go about developing features, based on his vast experience.

He cares about his projects and always brings full effort to provide top notch results. Mykhailo have developed numerous projects from scratch, or got integrated into existing teams and projects.

### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Nili Family Planner,** Israel, Tel Aviv — Lead Fullstack Developer

MARCH 2020

Developed the client's platform from scratch using VueJS and PHP backend. Also developed a mobile app using React Native. Worked closely with the team to add and maintain features.

## Freelance — Senior Fullstack Developer

**DECEMBER 2019 - MARCH 2020** 

Helping clients with their digital presence providing technical solutions for their needs - web apps (JS/PHP) and mobile applications (React Native).

## **PixelTech,** Ukraine, Zaporizhzhya — Lead Fullstack Developer

MAY 2016 - DECEMBER 2019

BestWebSoft, Ukraine, Zaporizhzhya — PHP/JS Developer

AUGUST 2012 - MAY 2019

#### **EDUCATION**

Zaporizhzhya National Technical University — Computer Engineering

2007 - 2012

## clubSRC.

#### **SKILLS**

Back-end:

Node.js, Express.js, Meteor.js, Sails.js, PHP, Laravel, Yil, WP/Woo, Magento 1/2.

DataBases:

MySQL, MongoDB, Firebase, GraphQL, PostgreSQL, Oracle, Redis.

Front-end:

React/Redux, Vue.js, TypeScript, Angular ½, React Native, Electron, Native Script, jQuery, CSS3+HTML5, LESS, SASS preprocessors.

Extra skills:

Integration of 3rd party APIs – social networks, payment systems, email systems and others.

GIT (BitBucket, GitLab etc) Task trackers: Jira, BaseCamp, Trello, Clickapp.

### **LANGUAGES**

Russian - Native English - Very good